19 it caught everyone by surprise
with increasing number of patients every
day our healthcare sector seemed
overwhelmed
at icici foundation
we have touched over half a million
lives by enabling them to a sustainable
livelihood
the call of the hour was to support the
overwhelmed health sector and stand by
the nation in this time of crisis
during the first wave we assisted covet
frontline warriors across the country
and equipped them with ppe kits masks
and sanitizers
the second wave of pandemic was sudden
and ferocious and brought out different
needs of healthcare system to provide
critical care support
patients in rural areas needed oxygen in
large capacity
thus we provided quality oxygen
concentrators in himalayan region and
tribal areas across india
there are a lot of these
flyby night operators coming up with
very low quality equipment but what icsa
foundation did was to first identify the
reliable manufacturers and stick to very
high quality we're very very happy that
not only did they support us but they
also supported us with very high quality
equipment
icici foundation continued to assist
hospitals and supported with ambulances
where bringing patients safely to a
hospital was a challenge
we also provided hospitals oxygen plants
where continuous oxygen supply was a
cause of concern
not just that hospitals that needed
continuous power supply were provided
suitable power backup systems
to save human lives we also provided
hospitals covert care centers across
india
not just that we also assisted in
setting up state-of-the-art covet care
hospital
[Music]
at icici foundation we believe that the
purpose of life is to be useful it is to
be compassionate towards human lives and
realize that you have lived and lived
well
[Music]
you